Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Pacific Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.4
            - South Pacific Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.4.8
              - 3097: Anchorages in the Friendly Islands, 11th July 1899 (revised 1959), 4436; blad
              - 3098: Vavau Group (Tonga or Friendly Islands), 30th April 1900 (last correction 1942), 4437; blad
              - 3148: Straat Salabangka to Straat Wowoni, 22nd March 1911 (last correction 1953), 4438; blad
              - 3250: Cape d'Urville to Wuvulu Island, 25th February 1943 (last correction 1955), 4439; blad
              - 3266: Plans in the Solomon Islands, 25th March 1955 (revised 1966), 4440; blad
              - 3268: Plans in the Solomon Islands, 27th January 1956 (revised 1961), 4441; blad
              - 3269: Anchorages in the Gilbert Islands, 23rd July 1948 (revised 1962), 4442; blad
              - 3402: Santa Isabel Island to New Georgia Group, 15th April 1955 (revised 1961), 4443; blad
              - 3403: Malaita Island to Santa Isabel Island, 17th September 1954 (last correction 1961), 4444; blad
              - 3404: Indispensable Strait, 20th November 1953 (last correction 1960), 4445; blad
              - 3412: San Cristóbal Island to Malaita Island, 6th May 1955 (last correction 1958), 4446; blad
              - 3413: Rua Sura Islands - Marau Sound - Danaë Bay, 29th March 1963, 4447; blad
              - 3416: New Georgia Group to Choiseul Island, 29th July 1955 (revised 1961), 4448; blad
              - 3419: Bougainvile Strait, 17th February 1956 (revised 1961), 4449; blad
              - 3419: Bougainville Strait, 17th February 1956 (revised 1961) (last correction 1967), 4450; blad
              - 3420: Bougainville Island, 9th March 1956 (revised 1961), 4451; blad
              - 3439: Plans in Santa Isabel Island, 11th February 1955, 4452; blad
              - 3553: Gazelle Peninsula and St. George's Channel, 25th January 1909 (last correction 1958), 4453; blad
              - 3553: Gazelle Peninsula and St. George's Channel, 25th January 1909 (revised 1989) (last correction 1992), 4454; blad
              - 3576: Anchorages in the Fiji Islands, 17th July 1906 (revised 1961), 4455; blad
              - 3664: Plans in archipel des Tuamotu, 9th July 1907 (last correction 1955), 4456; blad
              - 3731: Rade de Papeete, 26th June 1909 (revised 1962), 4457; blad
              - 3743: Patipi Baai to Tanjong Suaboor including McCluer Golf, 25th May 1920 (last correction 1958), 4458; blad
              - 3744: Tandjoeng Soeaboor to Kaboe eilanden including Misoöl and Kofiau eilanden, 7th July 1920 (last correction 1963), 4459; blad
              - 3745: Kaboe eilanden to Tandjoeng Kasbi including Sagewin and Dampier Straten and approaches and Waigeo, 2nd November 1920 (last correction 1962), 4460; blad
              - 3830: Bougainville Island to North Cape - New Ireland, 11th June 1934 (last correction 1958), 4461; blad
              - 3831: Hercules Bay to Sepik River and portion of New Britain, 11th June 1934 (last correction 1958), 4462; blad
              - 3832: North Cape, New Ireland to Wuvulu Island, 11th June 1934 (last correction 1958), 4463; blad
              - 3829: Plans in the Admiralty and Hermit Islands, 11th June 1934 (last correction 1958), 4464; blad
              - 3839: Horsburgh Light to Jason Bay, 26th July 1927 (last correction 1954), 4465; blad
              - 4624: Santa Cruz Islands to Butaritari, 5th March 1993, 4466; blad
              - 4638: Fiji to Kermadec Islands, 16th June 1989 (last correction 1992), 4467; blad
          - Polar Regions, B.2.7.3.2.5
            - Arctic, B.2.7.3.2.5.1
              - 275: Smith Sound, Kennedy and Robeson Channels, 20th April 1875 (last correction 1959), 4478; blad
            - Antarctic, B.2.7.3.2.5.2
              - 3170: The Antarctic - latitude 59º 27' to 75º s. and longitude 33º w. to 30º 28' e., 1st July 1955 (last correction 1957), 4468; blad
              - 3171: The Antarctic - latitude 52º 15' to 71º 17' s. and longitude 27º to 90º 27' E., 1st July 1955, 4469; blad
              - 3172: The Antarctic - latitude 52º 15' to 71º 17' s. and longitude 87º to 150º 27' E., 28th October 1955, 4470; blad
              - 3173: The Antarctic - latitude 59º 27' to 75º s. and longitude 147º to 149º w., 12th November 1954 (last correction 1957), 4471; blad
              - 3177: Ross Sea to South Pole, 29th March 1957, 4472; blad
              - 3205: South Shetland Islands and Bransfield Strait, 23rd September 1949 (last correction 1957), 4473; blad
              - 3213: Plans in Graham Land, 6th October 1950 (last correction 1956), 4474; blad
              - 3570: Brabant Island to Adelaide Island, 5th January 1951 (last correction 1958), 4475; blad
              - 3572: Bismarck Strait, 25th July 1958, 4476; blad
              - 3577: Adelaide Island - south western approaches, 14th August 1964 (revised 1983), 4477; blad
        - Nederlandse zeekaarten, B.2.7.3.3
          Nota bene: Zie ook rubriek B.2.7.3.1, inventarisnummers 2295 en 2296
          - 213: Curaçao, January 1938 (revised 1956), 4479; blad
          - 223: Curaçao, Bonaire en Aruba, January 1899 (revised 1954), 4480; blad
          - 1034 (D1B, 5B): Het Kanaal, Portland en The Casquets tot North Foreland en Oostende, June 1970 (revised 1982), 4481; blad
          - 1034 (D1B, 5B): Het Kanaal, Portland en The Casquets tot North Foreland en Oostende, June 1970 (revised 1987) (last correction 1992), 4482; blad
          - 1351 (D9): IJsselmeer, January 1982 (revised 1990), 4483; blad
          - 1454 (D9B): Waddenzee, Eierlandsche gronden en Den Haeder tot Harlingen, August 1960 (revised 1978) (last correction 1981), 4484; blad
          - 1454 (D9B): Waddenzee, Molengat tot Harlingen - Toegangen tot het IJsselmeer, March 1983 (revised 1989) (last correction 1992), 4485; blad
          - 1456 (D9): Terschellinger Gronden tot Harlingen, July 1992, 4486; blad
          - 1555: Eems en Dollard, Doekegat tot Delfzijl en Emden, October 1972 (revised 1984) (last correction 1992), 4487; blad
          - 1540: Rede Hoek van Holland en Europoort, July 1970 (revised 1973), 4488; blad
          - 1958 (D9): Nederlandse kust, Texel tot Borkum, April 1984, 4489; blad
          - 1971 (D2, D5): Sandettié tot Noord Hinder, 4490; blad
          - 1972 (D2): Noord Hinder tot Europoort, 4491; blad
          - 1974 (D2): IJ-Geul, approach to IJmuiden, 4492; blad
          - 2210: St. Maarten, Saba and St. Eustatius, November 1903 (revised 1956), 4493; blad
          - 2223: Curaçao, Bonaire en Aruba, January 1899 (revised 1954), 4494; blad
          - INT1043 - 1014, North Sea southern sheet, August 1973 (revised 1990) (last correction 1992), 4495; blad
          - INT1045 - 1037 (D7B en 9B)): Deutsche Bucht, June 1989 (revised 1992), 4496; blad
          - INT1046 - 1035 (D2A, 2E, 5B, 9B): Cap Gris Nez to Dogger Bight and Friesland Junction, June 1988 (revised 1990) (last correction 1992), 4497; blad
          - INT1046 - 1035 (D2A, 2E, 5B, 9B): Cap Gris Nez to Dogger Bight and Friesland Junction, June 1988 (revised 1994) (last correction 1996), 4498; blad
          - INT1413 - NL1353 (D9): Borkum tot Neuwerk en Helgoland, October 1988 (revised 1992), 4499; blad
          - INT1414 - NL2593: Texel to Borkum, March 1987 (last correction 1992), 4500; blad
          - INT1415 - NL2322: Goeree to Texel, October 1986 (revised 1991) (last correction 1992), 4501; blad
          - INT1416 - NL3371 (D): West Hinder and Outer Gabbard to Vlissingen and Scheveningen, June 1990 (last correction 1992), 4502; blad
          - INT1419 - NL1507 (D9): Friesland Junction to GW/EMS, October 1990 (last correction 1992), 4503; blad
          - INT1420 - NL1505 (D2E en 9B): Netherlands Gas Fields, October 1990 (last correction 1992), 4504; blad
          - INT1462 - 1555: Eems - Doekegat tot Pogum, date unknown, 4505; blad
          - INT1470 - 1546 (D9B): Zeegat van Texel en Rede Den Helder, January 1983 (last correction 1992), 4506; blad
          - INT1471 - NL124: Noordzeekanaal including IJmuiden, Zaandam and Amsterdam, August 1982 (revised 1991), 4507; blad
          - INT1472 - NL122 (D2): Approaches to Europoort and Hoek van Holland, September 1983 (revised 1991) (last correction 1992), 4508; blad
          - INT1473 - NL110 (D): Westkapelle to Stellendam and Maasvlakte, June 1985 (last correction 1992), 4509; blad
          - INT1474 - NL1442 (D2): Monding van de Westerschelde, van Oostende tot Westkapelle, November 1985 (revised 1989) (last correction 1990), 4510; blad
          - INT1476 - NL133: Nieuwe Maas and Oude Maas, Vlaardingen to IJsselmonde and Dordrecht, December 1981 (last correction 1992), 4511; blad
          - INT1477 - 1538: Dordtsche Kil, Hollandsch Diep to Noordschans, June 1985, 4512; blad
          - INT1479 - 1444: Westerschelde, Vlissingen to Baalhoek and Terneuzen-Gent Canal, October 1990 (last correction 1991), 4513; blad
          - INT1480 - 102 (D5): Van Duinkerke tot Oostende, March 1992, 4514; blad
          - INT1480 - 102 (D5): Van Duinkerke tot Oostende, February 1995 (revised 1994) (last correction 1995), 4515; blad
          - INT1481 - 1440 (D5): Calais to Dunkerque, April 1989 (last correction 1992), 4516; blad
          - INT1512 - 1348 (D): Nauw van Calais (Dover Strait|), Boulogne tot Zeebrugge en monding van de Thames, April 1992, 4517; blad
          - INT1704 - 1346 (D): New Haven tot Dover - Cap d'Antifer tot Cap Gris-Nez, October 1989 (last correction 1992), 4518; blad
        - Stroomkaarten, B.2.7.3.4
          - British Islands and adjacent waters, Atlas of Tides and Tidal Streams published by the Hydrographer of the Navy, June, 1941; 4519; stuk
          - British Islands and adjacent waters, Atlas of Tides and Tidal Streams, published by the Hydrographer of the Navy, April, 1946; 4520; stuk
          - Stroomatlas voor de Nederlandse kunst, uitgegeven door het ministerie van Marine, 1951; 4521; stuk
          - Kaartenatlas van het Nederlands Maritiem Instituut, bijlage bij Van Greenwich Boei tot Eurogeul, Oktober 1980; 4522; stuk
          - Wadatlas uitgegeven door het ministerie van Verkeer en Waterstaat, december 1989; 4523; stuk
          - Zwölf Stromkarten für jede Stunde der Tide bei Dover umfassend das Gebiet der südlichen Nordsee, des Englishen Kanals, des Bristol-Kanals und des Südlichen Theils vom Irischen Kanal, 4524; stuk
          - Stroomatlas, uitgegeven door de Chef der Hydrografie, 1992; 4525-4529; 5 stuk
            - Benedenrivieren en aanlopen: Hoek van Holland, Scheveningen, IJmuiden, Texel en Den Helder januari 1992, 4525; stuk
            - Noordzee januari 1992, 4526; stuk
            - Waddenzee, oost januari 1992, 4527; stuk
            - Waddenzee, west januari 1992, 4528; stuk
            - Westerschelde, Oosterschelde januari 1992, 4529; stuk
        - Hydrografische zeekaarten, B.2.7.3.5
          - North Sea Traffic Pattern published by the Netherlands Maritime Institute, datum onbekend; 4530; blad
          - Pilot Chart of the Central American Waters No. 3500, 1940; 4531; blad
          - Pilot Chart of the North Pacific Ocean No. 1401, 1962-1963; 4532-4544; 13 blad
            - February 1962, 4532; blad
            - March 1962, 4533; blad
            - April 1962, 4534; blad
            - September 1962, 4535; blad
            - December 1962, 4536; blad
            - January 1963, 4537; blad
            - February 1963, 4538; blad
            - May 1963, 4539; blad
            - June 1963, 4540; blad
            - July 1963, 4541; blad
            - August 1963, 4542; blad
            - October 1963, 4543; blad
            - November 1963, 4544; blad
          - Pilot Chart of the North Atlantic Ocean No. 1400, 1964; 4545; blad
          - 9313: Vinga - Göteborg, 1997, published by Sjöfartsverket, Norrköping, Sweden, 1983; 4546; blad
        - Hydrografische kaarten voor kust- en binnenwateren, B.2.7.3.6
          - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 1986; 4547; stuk
          - 1810 IJsselmeer met randmeren, 1989; 4548; stuk
          - Hydrografische kaart voor kust- en binnenwateren voor beroeps- en pleziervaart, 1991; 4549-4553; 5 stuk
            - 1801 Noordzeekust - Oostende tot Den Helder, 4549; stuk
            - 1803 Westerschelde - Vlissingen tot Antwerpen en Kanaal van Terneuzen naar Gent, 4550; stuk
            - 1809 Nieuwe waterweg, Nieuwe- en Oude Maas, Spui en Noord, Dordtsche Kil, Brielse Meer, 4551; stuk
            - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4552; stuk
            - 1812 Waddenzee (oostblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4553; stuk
          - Hydrografische kaart voor kust- en binnenwateren voor beroeps- en pleziervaart, 1992; 4554-4561; 8 stuk
            - 1801 Noordzeekust - Oostende tot Den Helder, 4554; stuk
            - 1803 Westerschelde - Vlissingen tot Antwerpen en Kanaal van Terneuzen naar Gent, 4555; stuk
            - 1805 Oosterschelde, Veerse Meer en Grevelingenmeer, 4556; stuk
            - 1807 Zoommeer, Volkerak en Spui, Haringvliet, Hollandsch Diep, 4557; stuk
            - 1809 Nieuwe Waterweg, Nieuwe- en Oude Maas, Spui en Noord, Dordtsche Kil, Brielse Meer, 4558; stuk
            - 1810 IJsselmeer met randmeren, 4559; stuk
            - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4560; stuk
            - 1812 Waddenzee (oostblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4561; stuk
          - Hydrografische kaart voor kust- en binnenwateren, 1994; 4562-4563; 2 stuk
            - 1801 Noordzeekust - Oostende tot Den Helder, 4562; stuk
            - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4563; stuk
          - Hydrografische kaart voor kust- en binnenwateren, 1995; 4564-4568; 5 stuk
            - 1801 Noordzeekust - De Panne tot Den Helder, 4564; stuk
            - 1803 Westerschelde - Vlissingen tot Antwerpen en Kanaal van Terneuzen naar Gent, 4565; stuk
            - 1805 Oosterschelde, Veerse Meer en Grevelingenmeer, 4566; stuk
            - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4567; stuk
            - 1812 Waddenzee (oostblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4568; stuk
          - Officiële zeekaart voor kust- en binnenwateren, 2001; 4569-4573; 5 blad
            - 1803 Zeeuwse en Zuidhollandse wateren - Westerschelde, Kanaal van Terneuzen naar Gent, Kanaal door Walcheren, Zoommeer, 4569; blad
              Nota bene: losbladige set van 5 bladen
            - 1809 Nieuwe Waterweg, Nieuwe- en Oude Maas, Spui en Noord, Dordtsche Kil, Brielse Meer, 4570; blad
              Nota bene: losbladige set van 6 bladen
            - 1810 IJsselmeer, Randmeren en Noordzeekanaal, 4571; blad
            - 1811 Waddenzee (westblad) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4572; blad
              Nota bene: losbladige set van 7 bladen
            - 1812 Waddenzee (oostelijk gedeelte) en aangrenzende Noordzeekust, 4573; blad
          - Officiële zeekaart voor kust- en binnenwateren, 2005; 4574-4575; 2 blad
            - 1803 Westerschelde - Vlissingen tot Antwerpen en Kanaal van Terneuzen naar Gent, 4574; blad
            - 1809 Nieuwe Waterweg, Nieuwe- en Oude Maas, Spui en Noord, Dordtsche Kil, Brielse Meer, 4575; blad
        - Hulpmiddelen, B.2.7.3.7
          - Dubbele parallellineaal, 2e helft 20e eeuw; 4576
      - Indexen op scheepsnamen, B.2.7.4
        - Register van ingekomen zaken vanaf 1962, dossiernummers 10692 tot en met 14494, 1962-1996; 2173; stuk
        - Index op scheepsnamen op de dossiers uitspraken en beschikkingen., 1909-1940; 450-453; 4 kaartenbakken
          - A - E, 450
          - F - L, 451
          - M - R, 452
          - S - Z, 453
        - Index op scheepsnamen A t/m Z, 1912-2010; 2174-2181; 8 kaartenbakken
          Nota bene: De index geeft toegang op de scheepsdossiers (inventarisnummers 571-2171); zie ook: Inleiding, aanwijzingen voor de gebruiker
          - A - B, 2174
          - C - E, 2175
          - F - H, 2176
          - I - L, 2177
          - M - N, 2178
          - O - Q, 2179
          - R - S, 2180
          - T - Z, 2181
        - Index op scheepsnamen op de dossiers uitspraken en beschikkingen, uit de periode na 1940., 1941 - c.1970; 454; kaartsysteem
        - Registers aangaande de uitspraken van de raad over de periode 1946 tot en met 1974, 1946-1967 en 1970-1974; 2182-2188; 1 pak en 6 stukken
          - 1946-1949, 2182
          - 1950-1952, 2183
          - 1953-1955, 2184
          - 1956-1959, 2185
          - 1960-1963, 2186
          - 1964-1967, 2187; pak
          - 1970-1974, 2188
        - Zaakregisters op scheepsnaam en monsterboekjes over de periode 1946-1979, 2189-2191; 3 stukken
          - 1946-1956, 2189
          - 1957-1979, 2190
          - 1963-1969, 2191
        - Register 'Uitspraken van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart vanaf 1 januari 1975', 1975-1986; 2192; stuk
          Nota bene: Bevat handgeschreven aantekeningen
        - Zaakregister op dossiernummer, 1980-1990; 2193; stuk
        - Register 'Uitspraken van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart vanaf 1 januari 1987', 1987-1996; 2194; stuk
        - Fiches met de strafmaat van personen, geclassificeerd op naam op alfabetische volgorde A t/m Z, 1909 - 2010; 2195
        - Lijsten van zaken op scheepsnaam en dossier over de periode 1991 tot en met 2002, en van zaken op de Nederlandse Antillen in de periode 1953 tot en met 2001, 2196; omslag
      - Uitspraken van de Raad, B.2.7.5
        - Uitspraken en beschikkingen van de raad, 1909-1916; 443-449
          Het betreft hier de officiële ondertekende uitspraken en beschikkingen. Vanaf 1917 zijn deze stukken in de betreffende dossiers opgenomen en is er geen aparte serie aanwezig.
          - 1909-1910, 443
          - 1911, 444
          - 1912, 445
          - 1913, 446
          - 1914, 447
          - 1915, 448
          - 1916, 449
        - Register der Uitspraken van den Raad voor de Scheepvaart, jaargangen 1910 tot en met 2009-2010, 1910-2010; 2197-2292; 96 delen
          - 1910, 2197
          - 1911, 2198
          - 1912, 2199
          - 1913, 2200
          - 1914, 2201
          - 1915, 2202
          - 1916, 2203
          - 1917, 2204
          - 1918, 2205
          - 1919, 2206
          - 1920-1921, 2207
          - 1922-1923, 2208
          - 1924, 2209
          - 1925, 2210
          - 1926, 2211
          - 1927, 2212
          - 1928, 2213
          - 1929, 2214
          - 1930, 2215
          - 1931, 2216
          - 1932, 2217
          - 1933, 2218
          - 1934, 2219
          - 1935, 2220
          - 1936, 2221
          - 1937, 2222
          - 1938, 2223
          - 1939, 2224
          - 1940, 2225
          - 1941, 2226
          - 1942, 2227
          - 1943-1944, 2228
          - 1945-1946, 2229
          - 1947, 2230
          - 1948, 2231
          - 1949, 2232
          - 1950, 2233
          - 1951, 2234
          - 1952, 2235
          - 1953, 2236
          - 1954, 2237
          - 1955, 2238
          - 1956, 2239
          - 1957, 2240
          - 1958, 2241
          - 1959, 2242
          - 1960, 2243
          - 1961, 2244
          - 1962, 2245
          - 1963, 2246
          - 1964, 2247
          - 1965, 2248
          - 1966, 2249
          - 1967, 2250
          - 1968, 2251
          - 1969, 2252
          - 1970, 2253
          - 1971, 2254
          - 1972, 2255
          - 1973, 2256
          - 1974, 2257
          - 1975, 2258
          - 1976, 2259
          - 1977, 2260
          - 1978, 2261
          - 1979, 2262
          - 1980, 2263
          - 1981, 2264
          - 1982, 2265
          - 1983, 2266
          - 1984, 2267
          - 1985, 2268
          - 1986, 2269
          - 1987, 2270
          - 1988, 2271
          - 1989, 2272
          - 1990, 2273
          - 1991, 2274
          - 1992, 2275
          - 1993, 2276
          - 1994, 2277
          - 1995, 2278
          - 1996, 2279
          - 1997, 2280
          - 1998, 2281
          - 1999, 2282
          - 2000, 2283
          - 2001, 2284
          - 2002, 2285
          - 2003, 2286
          - 2004, 2287
          - 2005, 2288
          - 2006, 2289
          - 2007, 2290
          - 2008, 2291
          - 2009-2010, 2292